<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<changes>
    <0.3.0>
        <header>Update 0.3.0 contains the following changes:</header>
        <change>Roughly 95-98% of the code has been rewritten and split into several new classes (was 15, is now 44).</change>
		<change>Endless Mode has been renamed to Infinity Mode.</change>
		<change>The main menu has been completely reworked, adding new submenus, new menu options, and customization options for Infinity Mode.</change>
		<change>The rendering pipeline has been rewritten and contains optimizations.</change>
		<change>The foundation for options (including control rebinding, audio mixing, graphic options, etc.) has been added.</change>
		<change>A new music track was added for exceptional successes in Infinity Mode.</change>
		<change>A new music track was added which plays before the first round in Infinity Mode.</change>
		<change>Rewrote many parts of the Audio class and changed how music is played and loaded into memory.</change>
		<change>Optimized all entities' code.</change>
		<change>Added capability to save user preferences (such as resolution, refresh rate, and audio volume).</change>
		<change>Framework for mouse controls has been added.</change>
		<change>The methodology for rendering has been redone.</change>
		<change>Rendering in layers have been added for consistent layering on the screen.</change>
		<change>Volume now scales linearly.</change>
		<change>The game speed is no longer tied to the frame rate.</change>
		<change>By default, the game now runs roughly at 60 FPS.</change>
		<change>Lots of minor bug fixes, timing issues, and graphical issues have been addressed.</change>
		<footer>(Note: Since nearly all of the code has been rewritten, it is basically a new engine framework. There will be many bugs that need to be 
		addressed before the port to LWJGL. Also, temporarily, the boss and the UI in the space fights have been removed. They will be added back 
		with patches/updates.</footer>
    </0.3.0>
	<0.3.X>
		<header>Upcoming update 0.3.X will contain the following changes:</header>
		<change>Implement a visual changelog.</change>
		<change>Rewrite how sprites and animations are handled.</change>
		<change>Functional mouse controls for the menu.</change>
		<change>Overhauled the functionality of the Wall.</change>
		<footer>There may be more to add as development continues.</footer>
	</0.3.X>
	<0.4>
		<header>Upcoming update 0.4.0 will contain the following changes:</header>
		<change>LWJGL will be included and used. This will increase the performance overhead.</change>
		<change>Engine will take advantage of multithreading.</change>
		<change>Reintroduce the pause menu.</change>
		<footer>There may be more to add as development continues. Also, a lot of bugs will likely introduced as the engine will be going through
		another large rewrite.</footer>
	</0.4>
</changes>
